{"Courses": [
    {
        "StudentIDs": [
            "4522",
            "6209"
        ],
        "description": "math1",
        "title": "math",
        "courseId": "C3981",
        "instructorId": "2870",
        "isCompleted": true,
        "status": "APPROVED",
        "lessons": [
            {
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "a",
                            "c",
                            "sd",
                            "as"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "a",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "sa",
                            "sd",
                            "das",
                            "das"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "sa",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "ds",
                            "sd",
                            "sd",
                            "sd"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "ds",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "ds",
                            "dsf",
                            "df",
                            "dff"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "ds",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "sdf",
                            "vf",
                            "fr",
                            "rg"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "sdf",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                    }
                ],
                "lessonId": "L0471",
                "title": "lesson1",
                "courseId": "C3981",
                "opResources": [],
                "content": "lesson1 content"
            },
            {
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "qew",
                            "eqwe",
                            "de",
                            "eds"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "eqwe",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "fe",
                            "fef",
                            "sef",
                            "fg"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "sef",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "hfh",
                            "fhg",
                            "hg",
                            "d"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "fhg",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "ht",
                            "h n",
                            "tn",
                            "fth"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "tn",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                    },
                    {
                        "options": [
                            "h",
                            "hf",
                            "fd",
                            "df"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": "hf",
                        "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                    }
                ],
                "lessonId": "L1429",
                "title": "lesson 2",
                "courseId": "C3981",
                "opResources": [],
                "content": "lesson2 content"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "StudentIDs": ["6209"],
        "description": "hhhh",
        "title": "new",
        "courseId": "C3221",
        "instructorId": "3926",
        "isCompleted": false,
        "status": "APPROVED",
        "lessons": [{
            "questions": [],
            "lessonId": "L8135",
            "title": "l1",
            "courseId": "C3221",
            "opResources": [],
            "content": "few"
        }]
    },
    {
        "StudentIDs": ["6209"],
        "description": "kjoj",
        "title": "hi",
        "courseId": "C7102",
        "instructorId": "3926",
        "isCompleted": false,
        "status": "APPROVED",
        "lessons": []
    }
]}